<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Dan Crowther</title>
    <link>/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Dan Crowther</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 21 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Welcome to my website - why is it here?</title>
      <link>/posts/welcome/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/welcome/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to my website.
The aim of this website is to try and showcase who I am and where I am going with my video projects both personally and at College so you can get a feel of my journey with video
I want to share with people the technology I used to create this platform that will enable me to share my portfolio as a showcase of my work in video</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting started - Part 1 - the thought process</title>
      <link>/posts/gettingstarted_part1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/gettingstarted_part1/</guid>
      <description>I thought it was time to setup some form of central repository or portfolio of my work when I started visiting university open days and wanted to be able to showcase my work so far. This article aims to outline the initial steps take to get off the gound.
Currently the content I have created exists in a number of places. Some exists on YouTube in private channels and some exists at College in private server locations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting started - Part 2 - the practicalities</title>
      <link>/posts/gettingstarted_part2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/gettingstarted_part2/</guid>
      <description>After a bit of a crach course in googling how to do things its time to join all the dots&amp;hellip;
Hugo Installing Hugo was fairly painless and it has some great features like the ability to preview my changes on the fly.
I then found a simple theme from the Hugo themes library https://jamstackthemes.dev/theme/hugo-theme-cleanwhite/ which should allow me to use a simple blog structure and menu items
I did some basic customisation of the theme so Hugo is ready to go</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adding the actual content - the nitty gritty</title>
      <link>/posts/addingcontent/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/addingcontent/</guid>
      <description>In some respects this was the easiest part. Early on I needed to decide the structure and it made sense to keep it fairly simple.
The default landing page will have my &amp;ldquo;blog posts&amp;rdquo; that are a history of what I am doing or have done.
There will be an archive of all my posts by date so a historical timeline will be seen over time
There will be the main portfolio section that can be accessed from the main home page</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Portfolio - my video content</title>
      <link>/posts/myportfolio/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/myportfolio/</guid>
      <description>Ultimately the aim of this website is to share some of the videos and content that I have created - so here it is&amp;hellip;.
My Portfolio
In future you can simply select My Portfolio from the menu in the top right hand corner</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Livestream test</title>
      <link>/posts/portfolio_livestreamtest/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/portfolio_livestreamtest/</guid>
      <description>This was an experiment in live streaming and person following
We have an Aver tracking camera that can track people or objects. What we wanted to do was evaluate the effectiveness of this when livestreaming a basketball game
We took the Aver Camera on a tripod, an IPad Mini, a mini network switch and wifi access point and paired all of this up with a mobile hotspot on a phone</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Basketball end of season highlights</title>
      <link>/posts/portfolio_endofseason/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/portfolio_endofseason/</guid>
      <description>This was a video that I edited and put together for a basketball end of season highlights celebration
Every game that this particular team play is recorded as a simple video file and then I took all of the best moments from these and added an audio track and this was presented at the club awards and presentation night</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Basketball promotional video</title>
      <link>/posts/portfolio_foundation/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/portfolio_foundation/</guid>
      <description>I am a player at Abingdon Eagles Basketball club, however I am also a coach and official.
One of my honours is to be asked to coach for a Community Session setup by the Abingdon Eagles Foundation (https://abingdoneagles.foundation). Every Monday I am an assistant coach for Walking Basketball where people are returning from illness or simply want to play basketball or need some community around them.
The Foundation is funded via external grants that have to be appled for so we decided to create a promotional video showing just what we do.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
