<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>portfolio on Dan Crowther</title>
    <link>/tags/portfolio/</link>
    <description>Recent content in portfolio on Dan Crowther</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 19 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/portfolio/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Livestream test</title>
      <link>/posts/portfolio_livestreamtest/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/portfolio_livestreamtest/</guid>
      <description>This was an experiment in live streaming and person following
We have an Aver tracking camera that can track people or objects. What we wanted to do was evaluate the effectiveness of this when livestreaming a basketball game
We took the Aver Camera on a tripod, an IPad Mini, a mini network switch and wifi access point and paired all of this up with a mobile hotspot on a phone</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Basketball end of season highlights</title>
      <link>/posts/portfolio_endofseason/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/portfolio_endofseason/</guid>
      <description>This was a video that I edited and put together for a basketball end of season highlights celebration
Every game that this particular team play is recorded as a simple video file and then I took all of the best moments from these and added an audio track and this was presented at the club awards and presentation night</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Basketball promotional video</title>
      <link>/posts/portfolio_foundation/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/portfolio_foundation/</guid>
      <description>I am a player at Abingdon Eagles Basketball club, however I am also a coach and official.
One of my honours is to be asked to coach for a Community Session setup by the Abingdon Eagles Foundation (https://abingdoneagles.foundation). Every Monday I am an assistant coach for Walking Basketball where people are returning from illness or simply want to play basketball or need some community around them.
The Foundation is funded via external grants that have to be appled for so we decided to create a promotional video showing just what we do.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
