<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Jamstack on Dan Crowther</title>
    <link>/tags/jamstack/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Jamstack on Dan Crowther</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 21 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/jamstack/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Welcome to my website - why is it here?</title>
      <link>/posts/welcome/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/welcome/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to my website.
The aim of this website is to try and showcase who I am and where I am going with my video projects both personally and at College so you can get a feel of my journey with video
I want to share with people the technology I used to create this platform that will enable me to share my portfolio as a showcase of my work in video</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting started - Part 1 - the thought process</title>
      <link>/posts/gettingstarted_part1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/gettingstarted_part1/</guid>
      <description>I thought it was time to setup some form of central repository or portfolio of my work when I started visiting university open days and wanted to be able to showcase my work so far. This article aims to outline the initial steps take to get off the gound.
Currently the content I have created exists in a number of places. Some exists on YouTube in private channels and some exists at College in private server locations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting started - Part 2 - the practicalities</title>
      <link>/posts/gettingstarted_part2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/gettingstarted_part2/</guid>
      <description>After a bit of a crash course in googling how to do things its time to join all the dots&amp;hellip;
Hugo Installing Hugo was fairly painless and it has some great features like the ability to preview my changes on the fly.
I then found a simple theme from the Hugo themes library https://jamstackthemes.dev/theme/hugo-theme-cleanwhite/ which should allow me to use a simple blog structure and menu items
I did some basic customisation of the theme so Hugo is ready to go</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
